<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gson Typetoken on Simple Solution</title>
    <link>https://simplesolution.dev/tag/gson-typetoken/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gson Typetoken on Simple Solution</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 10:25:52 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://simplesolution.dev/tag/gson-typetoken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Convert classpath resource JSON File to Java Object using Gson</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-classpath-resource-json-file-to-java-object-using-gson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 10:25:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-classpath-resource-json-file-to-java-object-using-gson/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Gson tutorial, we show you how to read a JSON file from classpath resources and convert the JSON content to Java object using the Gson library and Apache Commons IO library. By different Java example programs we learn how to convert JSON content to a HashMap, a List of Map, an object of a custom defined class or a List of objects.
   (adsbygoogle = window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert JSON File to Java Object in Java using Gson</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-json-file-to-java-object-using-gson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:22:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-json-file-to-java-object-using-gson/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Gson tutorial we learn how to convert a JSON file into a Java object using the Gson class of the Gson library. By different Java example programs we show you how to convert a JSON file into a HashMap object, a list of Map, an object of custom defined classes or a List of objects.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  How to add Gson to the Java project To use the Gson library in the Gradle build project, add the following dependency into the build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert JSON String to Java Object in Java using Gson</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-json-string-to-java-object-using-gson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 22:52:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-convert-json-string-to-java-object-using-gson/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Gson tutorial we learn how to use the Gson library to convert a JSON String into a Java object by using Gson class. Via different Java code examples we show you how to convert a JSON String into Java HashMap, an object of a custom defined class or a List of objects.
   (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  How to add Gson to the Java project To use the Gson library in the Gradle build project, add the following dependency into the build.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>