<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Java Tutorials on Simple Solution</title>
    <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Java Tutorials on Simple Solution</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:18:09 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://simplesolution.dev/java-tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Gson Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-gson-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 23:18:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-gson-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Gson tutorial we learn how to use the Gson library.
Serializes Java Object to JSON String  How to convert Java object to JSON String
 How to generate Pretty Print JSON String
 Gson.toJson() code examples
  Deserializes JSON String to Java Object  How to convert JSON String to Java object
 How to convert JSON String to JsonElement object
 How to use TypeToken class</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Google Guava Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-google-guava-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:08:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-google-guava-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Google Guava tutorial we learn how to use the Google Guava library.
com.google.common.base.CaseFormat class  How to convert between Case Format of String  com.google.common.base.Ascii class  How to truncate String
 How to check Character is UPPERCASE
 How to check ASCII Character is lowercase
 How to check two ASCII Strings Equals Ignore Case
 How to convert ASCII String to UPPERCASE
 How to convert ASCII String to lowercase</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Log4j Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-log4j-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 23:20:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-log4j-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Log4j tutorial we learn how to use the Log4j library.
 Log4j 2 Properties Configuration with Console Appender
 Log4j 2 YAML Configuration with Console Appender
 Log4j 2 XML Configuration with Console Appender
 Log4j 2 JSON Configuration with Console Appender
  Happy Coding 😊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache PDFBox Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-pdfbox-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 23:11:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-pdfbox-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache PDFBox tutorial we learn how to use the Apache PDFBox library.
 How to create PDF document page labels
 How to create Bookmarks for PDF document
 How to add Metadata to PDF document
 How to insert image to PDF document
 How to create PDF document file
  Happy Coding 😊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache POI Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-poi-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 23:07:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-poi-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache POI tutorial we learn how to use the Apache POI library.
 How to hide and unhide Excel row
 How to create multiple fonts Excel cell using RichTextString
 Spring Boot Web Application Download Excel File
 How to update Excel file content
 How to use Excel cell fonts
 How to merge Excel cells
 Excel Cell Background Foreground and Font Color
 Excel Cell Border and Border Color</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons Text Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-text-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:52:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-text-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons Text tutorial we learn how to use the Apache Commons Text library.
 How to escape or unescape String for CSV column data
 How to convert words in a String into camelCase
 How to substitute a String by replace variables map to Template String
 How to uncapitalize first character of all words in a String
 How to swap Lowercase and Uppercase of a String</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java ZXing Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-zxing-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:47:14 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-zxing-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java ZXing tutorial we learn how to use the ZXing library.
 How to read QR code from image file or Base64 String
 How to generate QR code
  Happy Coding 😊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java OSHI Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-oshi-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:28:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-oshi-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java OSHI tutorial, we learn how to use the OSHI library.
 How to get file system information
 How to get virtual memory information
 How to get physical memory or RAM information
 How to get CPU information
 How to get operating system information
  Happy Coding 😊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java jsoup tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-jsoup-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:25:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-jsoup-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java jsoup tutorial, we learn how to use the jsoup library.
 How to convert HTML into Plain Text
 How to pretty print XML String and XML file
 How to get all HTML elements
 How to clean HTML String to get safe HTML from untrusted HTML String
 How to get HTML elements by attribute value
 How to get HTML elements by attribute name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons CSV Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-csv-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:19:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-csv-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons CSV tutorial we learn how to use the Apache Commons CSV library.
Write CSV File  How to write and read CSV file  Read and Parse CSV Content  How to read and parse CSV file
 How to read and parse CSV content from an URL
 How to read and parse CSV content from a String
 Top 3 Libraries for Writing and Reading CSV File</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons Compress Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-compress-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 22:14:42 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-compress-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons Compress Tutorial we learn how to use the Apache Commons Compress library.
How to use Apache Commons Compress with .zip files  Extract .zip File
 Create .zip File
  Happy Coding 😊</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Joda Time Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-joda-time-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 21:51:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-joda-time-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Joda Time tutorial, we learn how to use different classes of the Joda Time library.
org.joda.time.DateTime class  How to use DateTime by Examples
 How to get Date and Time fields value of DateTime object
 How to create DateTime with Time End of the Day
 How to compare Joda-Time DateTime using DateTimeComparator
 How to format DateTime String using ISODateTimeFormat
 Ho to convert DateTime into Calendar and Vice Versa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons Codec Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-codec-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:32:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-codec-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons Codec Tutorial we learn how to use the Java Apache Commons Codec library.
org.apache.commons.codec.binary.BinaryCodec class  Encode and Decode String to Binary Format  org.apache.commons.codec.binary.Base32 class  Base32 Encoding and Decoding  org.apache.commons.codec.binary.Base64 class  How to encode a String into Base64
 How to encode byte array into Base64 format
 How to encode a String into Base64 format
 How to encode byte array into Base64 format</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons IO Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-io-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:02:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-io-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons IO Tutorial we learn how to use the Java Apache Commons IO library.
org.apache.commons.io.FileUtils class  How to get Files in Directory based on Cutoff Time
 How to check a File is Symlink or Actual File
 How to get User Home Directory
 How to get System Temporary Directory
 How to create New Directory
 How to delete File
 How to delete Directory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Apache Commons Lang Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-lang-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 23:28:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-apache-commons-lang-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java Apache Commons Lang Tutorial we learn how to use the Apache Commons Lang 3 library.
org.apache.commons.lang3.CharUtils class  How to check Character is ASCII Printable
 How to check Character is ASCII Numeric
 How to check Character is ASCII Control Character
 How to check Character is ASCII
 How to check Character is ASCII Alphabetic Upper Case
 How to check Character is ASCII Alphanumeric</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java CommonMark Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-commonmark-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:53:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-commonmark-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this Java CommonMark Tutorial we learn how to use the commonmark-java library and extensions.
How to use the commonmark-java library  How to parse Markdown to HTML
 How to parse Markdown to HTML with Spring Boot
  CommonMark Java Extensions How to use CommonMark GFM Tables Extension
 How to use CommonMark Autolink Extension
 How to use CommonMark Strikethrough Extension
 How to use CommonMark Heading Anchor Extension</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Imgscalr Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://simplesolution.dev/java-imgscalr-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 21:59:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simplesolution.dev/java-imgscalr-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This Imgscalr Tutorial we learn how to use the Imgscalr library for image operations.
Resize Image  How to Resize Image File
 How to Resize Images in Directory
 Spring Boot Upload and Resize Images
  Generate Thumbnail Images  How to Create Thumbnail Image
 How to Create High Quality Thumbnail Images
  Scale Image  How to Scale Image File  Crop Image  How to Crop Image to Square</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>